Contact

terriejmitch@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/terrie-mitchell-1ab96055 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

BLS

Nursing

Patient Safety

Terrie Mitchell

Nurse Manager-Nights for Surgical and Liver ICU Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Current Nurse Manager for a 28 bed Surgical and Liver ICU in the Texas Medical Center. Experienced Staff Nurse, travel nurse, Pediatric Home Health nurse prior to current position. Skilled in various Critical Care settings as well as Medical-Surgical experience. Strong healthcare services professional enhanced through a Master's degree focused in Nursing Administration from The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston (UTHealth). Previous Manager, House/Strike Team Supervisor, which consisted of coordination of transfers and admissions to and from Micro hospitals in both Kansas and Indiana. In addition, was lead coordinator of staff hiring and orientation.

Experience

Houston Methodist Night Nurse Manager March 2019 - Present (1 year 3 months) Houston, Texas Area

NursesRx

Travel Registered Nurse June 2018 - March 2019 (10 months)

Experienced gained as travel nurse for CVICU, SICU, and general ICU in Houston, TX as well as Burbank, CA.

Tandem Hospital Partners, LLC House Supervisor/ Strike Team May 2017 - April 2018 (1 year)

Houston, Texas Area

Responsibilities include developing and coordinating training schedules and content for new hires of RNs, Paramedics and Radiology Techs for new Micro Hospitals in the Midwest. Collaboration with multiple markets for hospital specific needs and workflows. Initiating and completing transfers and

admissions to and from the Micro Hospitals along with remaining constant resource person for multiple hospitals in multiple State markets.

Houston Methodist
Registered Nurse
June 2011 - June 2017 (6 years 1 month)

Epic Health Services, Inc.

Pediatric Staff Nurse

August 2016 - January 2017 (6 months)

Beaumont/Port Arthur, Texas Area

Baptist Hospitals of Southeast Texas Staff Nurse January 2016 - January 2017 (1 year 1 month) Beaumont/Port Arthur, Texas Area

Wonderful experience working in the Medical Intensive Care Unit for this facility. Due relocation, my time here was limited but the experience gained was limitless.

Education

The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston (UTHealth)

Master's degree, Nursing Administration · (2015 - 2017)

Prairie View A&M University

Bachelor of Science in Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2008 - 2012)

Prairie View A&M University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse